2016 holds for all of us as individuals, but what it terms is our community also that we love and where
we have chosen to live and so far, are just asked that you would bless it give our leaders wisdom as they
lead in what is best for all community. We do pray
if Councilman Joe Sharbet I know he talked a land at Houston
having some tough days but fathered us around the family with your presence once again
and fathered the opportunity just to lift our community up in prayer. Jesus name, amen
to address the authority on any of your via gen 9. Yes sir, I'm forward
you do not need that three minutes and then must be tough for
I'm working on the clock, all right.
And you need to state your name please?
My name is Rich Moomerd and i am a resident of
The Great City at Miami
And i'm here to say Happy New Year
To all of you and I wanted
Some nice things about our police department
Maybe not four minutes
What is this election?
Oh, well
All right. I want a table
Some people may know that some young
They are not, they have interesting neighbors move their next door
Not too long ago
And there was a lot of all the same
Most popular neighbors I've ever seen
Several cars showing up and so
i'm just, almost 1st for neighbor
Somewhat
Obviously could do much as
Just a citizen
The police department did a fantastic job
Getting out
Getting on top of that and very shortly
The house was raided
And i got to say I just happened
To be home when it is raided
It wasn't awesome
And we are the chief
That goes through
So, about what's pretty neat
Or get found up, you do before a football game
So, it has to be a pretty good rush
And what was the phenomenal job?
It is quick
As far as you know
The notification and then they got
Information that
They needed
A great Job
I don't get enough aquerates
And so i wanted to do that
Thank you all
Very much for the presentation
We're going to make a statement
I'm not gonna say it's in a fair by watching
About 30 police officers we have
Almost 15,000 citizens
So those eyes and ears out there like rich was
That is very important
If your situation liked this
You are never near home
That you are uncomfortable with
Please do not hesitate to contact chief Anderson
Any of the tech news or
Members far police department
Because we certainly will be proactive
And just for a minute that's pretty impressive
I don't know your
Okay
Item number
Email is for move on
Item 5
Item 5 is the
Consent agenda
Stab with recommending
Adam 6 through 9 for consent agenda
With a no questions
I'd entertain emotion
Question
No this agenda you are okay
11 staff reports
Those were in your package
There's a question
And item 13 is a German
We have the most to adjourn
In second slide
Question
Alright
So we are not going